[{"answer": "And then I hear this rabbi on television, I mean imagine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Ya know, I was just a little surprised", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Well, scintillating as always", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm going shopping with my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm going shopping with my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Clothes shopping", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes I did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No I wasn't able to sip it in my normal fashion", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No I wasn't able to sip it in my normal fashion", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well I think I take a normal sip", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hm Hm. All right, all right. You take big sips", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "O.K. You take normal sips. Nothing wrong with that. Then what happened", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, see they like to sell their own coffee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah that's going to be a problem. It's gonna be a problem for them. This a clear violation of your rights as a consumer. It's an infringement on your constitutional rights. It's outrageous, egregious, preposterous", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No. They put the top on", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What I mean who ever heard of this anyway? Suing a company because there coffee is too hot? Coffee is supposed to be hot", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " my friend says the top was faulty.", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, ya know you haven't been around for a while", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh that place huh? Hear that my friend? That's in that place", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I might be my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What, he can't jump out of the chair? How long does that take? Here look at this.  Here, watch.  Criminals. Boom. I'm up.  Stop It! Stop It! Stop It", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Would you get out of here. Who's gonna turn down a chair? I would be very interested to know how he felt about all of this. Maybe I'll have a talk with him", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, so", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, I mean don't you think that he was probably called Maestro while he was conducting, not in social situations. I mean his friends probably just called him my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well I put that Chinese balm on that the Maestro gave me. And look, it healed it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "So? My lawsuit. I'm finished", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't need a chair", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I did at first, but actually I kind of got used to it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I am not calling you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "O.K. from now on I want you to call me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Why not you call him Maestro", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Oh I missed the Maestro", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Huh. Your renting a house in that place", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It it's huge. It's probably like that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "It's a big region", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yeah and", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "So are you gonna get him a chair", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You've got to stop it. Your your all hopped up on the caffein", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Common my friend, this guy is crazy. Get out.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I didn't push you. How much did you pay that guy", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "75,000 lira? Are you out of your mind", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Maestro.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Oh, conversion rate, oh", "qsentId": 48}]